pbfantasy.com 2008-06-04

# Philippine Basketball Fantasy - Website Info

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy discloses what information PBFantasy gathers and how PBFantasy uses it. Please read this privacy policy before using PBFantasy ("the Site") or submitting any personal information. By using the Site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. 

COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

PBFantasy collects personally identifiable information, like names, birth date, gender, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors during registration. PBFantasy also collects information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. 

USE OF INFORMATION

PBFantasy uses any information you voluntarily provide to enhance your experience in our network of Sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the Sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users. The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you have previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. 

PBFantasy uses tracking information to determine which areas of our Sites users prefer like based on traffic to those areas. PBFantasy does not track what individual users read, but rather the overall performance of each page. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. PBFantasy creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. Because PBFantasy does not track the usage patterns of individual users, an advertiser or sponsor will never know that a specific user clicked its ad. 

SHARING AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

PBFantasy uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. This is essential in keeping our service free. PBFantasy does not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public. PBFantasy may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. PBFantasy may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. 

CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

PBFantasy operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to the information provided by our users. 

CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

PBFantasy reserves the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive, basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the Site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide is used. 

PRIVACY CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us.
